var employees = [
    { "question" : "Question?.", "answer" : "answer"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the noun invention?.", "answer" : "invent"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the noun observation?.", "answer" : "observe"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the noun behaviour?.", "answer" : "behave"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the noun association?.", "answer" : "associate"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the noun Saying?.", "answer" : "say"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the noun Proof?.", "answer" : "prove"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the verb (to) invent?.", "answer" : "invention"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the verb (to) observe?.", "answer" : "observation"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the verb (to) behave?.", "answer" : "behaviour"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the verb (to) associate?.", "answer" : "association"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the verb (to) say?.", "answer" : "saying"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the verb (to) prove?.", "answer" : "proof"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the verb surprise?.", "answer" : "surprisingly"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the noun day?.", "answer" : "daily"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adverb daily?.", "answer" : "day"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun day?.", "answer" : "daily"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective daily?.", "answer" : "day"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun sympathy?.", "answer" : "sympathetic"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective sympathetic?.", "answer" : "sympathy"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun reason?.", "answer" : "reasonable"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective reasonable?.", "answer" : "reason"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun challenge?.", "answer" : "challenging"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective challenging?.", "answer" : "challenge"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun refresh?.", "answer" : "refreshing"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective refreshing?.", "answer" : "refresh"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective negative of the adjective likely?.", "answer" : "unlikely"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective positive of the adjective unlikely?.", "answer" : "likely"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective negative of the adjective positive honest?.", "answer" : "dishonest"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective positive of the adjective negative dishonest?.", "answer" : "honest"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective negative of the adjective positive  usual?.", "answer" : "unusual"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective positive of the adjective negative unusual?.", "answer" : "usual"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective negative of the adjective regular?.", "answer" : "irregular"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective positive of the adjective irregular?.", "answer" : "regular"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective negative of the adjective suitable?.", "answer" : "unsuitable"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective positive of the adjective unsuitable?.", "answer" : "suitable"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective negative of the adjective able?.", "answer" : "unable"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective positive of the adjective unable?.", "answer" : "able"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective negative of the adjective polite?.", "answer" : "impolite"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective positive of the adjective impolite?.", "answer" : "polite"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective positive of the adjective popular?.", "answer" : "unpopular"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective negative  of the adjective unpopular?.", "answer" : "popular"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective negative unpopular?.", "answer" : "popularity"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective positive popular?.", "answer" : "popularity"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective negative of the noun popularity?.", "answer" : "unpopular"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective positive of the noun popularity?.", "answer" : "popular"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the verb (to) use?.", "answer" : "useful"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the adjective useful?.", "answer" : "use"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the verb (to) remark?.", "answer" : "remarkable"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the adjective remarkable?.", "answer" : "remark"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the verb (to) choose?.", "answer" : "choosy"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the adjective choosy?.", "answer" : "choose"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the verb (to) impress?.", "answer" : "impressed"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the adjective impressed?.", "answer" : "impress"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the verb (to) attract?.", "answer" : "attractive"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the adjective attractive?.", "answer" : "attract"},


    { "question" : "What is the other noun of the noun sun?.", "answer" : "sunshine"},
    { "question" : "What is the other noun of the noun sunshine?.", "answer" : "sun"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the verb (to) fascinate?.", "answer" : "fascinated"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the adjective fascinated?.", "answer" : "fascinate"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the adjective predictable?.", "answer" : "predict"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the verb (to) predict?.", "answer" : "predictable"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the verb (to) help?.", "answer" : "helpful"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the adjective helpful?.", "answer" : "help"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun cheek?.", "answer" : "cheeky"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective cheeky?.", "answer" : "cheek"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun aggression?.", "answer" : "aggressive"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective aggressive?.", "answer" : "aggression"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun child?.", "answer" : "childish"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective childish?.", "answer" : "child"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the verb (to) relax?.", "answer" : "relaxing"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the adjective relaxing?.", "answer" : "relax"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the adjective reliable?.", "answer" : "rely"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the verb (to) rely?.", "answer" : "reliable"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the verb (to) decision?.", "answer" : "decisive"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the adjective decisive?.", "answer" : "decision"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the verb (to) terrify?.", "answer" : "terrified"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the adjective terrified?.", "answer" : "terrify"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the verb (to) astonish?.", "answer" : "astonished"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the adjective astonished?.", "answer" : "astonish"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the verb (to) exhaust?.", "answer" : "exhausted"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the adjective exhausted?.", "answer" : "exhaust"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the verb (to) compete?.", "answer" : "competitive"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective competent?.", "answer" : "competence"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the the verb (to) compete?.", "answer" : "competition"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the the noun competition?.", "answer" : "compete"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the  noun competence?.", "answer" : "competent"},


    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the verb (to) organise?.", "answer" : "organised"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the adjective organised?.", "answer" : "organise"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective organised?.", "answer" : "organisation"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the the verb (to) organise?.", "answer" : "organisation"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the the noun organisation?.", "answer" : "organise"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the  noun organisation?.", "answer" : "organised"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun practice?.", "answer" : "practical"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective practical?.", "answer" : "practice"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective negative of the noun patient?.", "answer" : "impatient"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective negative  impatient?.", "answer" : "patient"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun fool?.", "answer" : "foolish"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective foolish?.", "answer" : "fool"},


    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun puzzle?.", "answer" : "puzzling"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective puzzling?.", "answer" : "puzzle"},


    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun artist?.", "answer" : "artistic"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective artistic?.", "answer" : "artist"},


    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun caution?.", "answer" : "cautious"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective cautious?.", "answer" : "caution"},


    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun energy?.", "answer" : "energetic"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective energetic?.", "answer" : "energy"},


    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun greed?.", "answer" : "greedy"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective greedy?.", "answer" : "greed"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun pessimist?.", "answer" : "pessimistic"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective pessimistic?.", "answer" : "pessimist"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun centre?.", "answer" : "central"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective central?.", "answer" : "centre"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun success?.", "answer" : "successful"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective successful?.", "answer" : "success"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun courage?.", "answer" : "courageous"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective courageous?.", "answer" : "courage"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun advantage?.", "answer" : "advantageous"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective advantageous?.", "answer" : "advantage"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun coast?.", "answer" : "coastal"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective coastal?.", "answer" : "coast"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun economy?.", "answer" : "economical"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective economical?.", "answer" : "economy"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun industry?.", "answer" : "industrial"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective industrial?.", "answer" : "industry"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun tropic?.", "answer" : "tropical"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective tropical?.", "answer" : "tropic"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun delight?.", "answer" : "delighted"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective delighted?.", "answer" : "delight"},


    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun storm?.", "answer" : "stormy"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective stormy?.", "answer" : "storm"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun content?.", "answer" : "content"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective content?.", "answer" : "content"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun director?.", "answer" : "direct"},
    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective direct?.", "answer" : "director"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the the verb (to) meet?.", "answer" : "meeting"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the the noun meeting?.", "answer" : "meet"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the the verb (to) inhabit?.", "answer" : "inhabitant"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the the noun inhabitant?.", "answer" : "inhabit"},


    { "question" : "What is the noun of the the verb (to) choose?.", "answer" : "choice"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the the noun choice?.", "answer" : "choose"},


    { "question" : "What is the noun of the the verb (to) grow?.", "answer" : "growth"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the the noun growth?.", "answer" : "grow"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the the verb (to) employ?.", "answer" : "employment"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the the noun employment?.", "answer" : "employ"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the the verb (to) agree?.", "answer" : "agreement"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the the noun agreement?.", "answer" : "agree"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the the verb (to) lose?.", "answer" : "loss"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the the noun loss?.", "answer" : "lose"},


    { "question" : "What is the noun of the the verb (to) decide?.", "answer" : "decision"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the the noun decision?.", "answer" : "decide"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the the verb (to) pay?.", "answer" : "payment"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the the noun payment?.", "answer" : "pay"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the the verb (to) operate?.", "answer" : "operation"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the the noun operation?.", "answer" : "operate"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the the verb (to) solve?.", "answer" : "solution"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the the noun solution?.", "answer" : "solve"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the the verb (to) concentrate?.", "answer" : "concentration"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the the noun concentration?.", "answer" : "concentrate"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the the verb (to) expand?.", "answer" : "expansion"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the the noun expansion?.", "answer" : "expand"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the  adverb automatically?.", "answer" : "automatic"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the the adjective automatic?.", "answer" : "automatically"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the  adverb highly?.", "answer" : "high"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the the adjective high?.", "answer" : "highly"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the  adverb annually?.", "answer" : "annual"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the the adjective annual?.", "answer" : "annually"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the  adverb easily?.", "answer" : "easy"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the the adjective easy?.", "answer" : "easily"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective  of the  adverb positive evenly?.", "answer" : "uneven"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb positive of the the adjective  uneven?.", "answer" : "evenly"},

    { "question" : "What is the adjective  of the  adverb negative unevenly?.", "answer" : "uneven"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb negative of the the adjective uneven?.", "answer" : "unevenly"},


    { "question" : "(of a person) of unknown name?.", "answer" : "anonymous"},
    { "question" : "A trick or deception?.", "answer" : "hoax"},
    { "question" : "A container filled with explosives?.", "answer" : "bomb"},
    { "question" : "To do physical harm or damage?.", "answer" : "injure"},
    { "question" : "To plan and direct a scheme or plot?.", "answer" : "mastermind"},
    { "question" : "A person who takes part in a secret plan to do something unlawful?.", "answer" : "conspirator"},
    { "question" : "An explosive powder?.", "answer" : "gunpowder"},
    { "question" : "The group of people who are responsible for making laws in some forms of government?.", "answer" : "gunpowder"},
    { "question" : "Someone who strongly and publicly disagrees with the government?.", "answer" : "dissident"},
    { "question" : "The group of people who belong to the highest social class in some countries?.", "answer" : "nobility"},
    { "question" : "A secret plan to do something, usually illegal?.", "answer" : "nobility"},
    { "question" : "To explode?.", "answer" : "blow up"},
    { "question" : "People who have special titles such as duke, duchess and often own lots of land?.", "answer" : "blow up"},
    { "question" : "The people who watch a film in a cinema or theatre?.", "answer" : "Audience"},
    { "question" : "Something that you buy at a very good price?.", "answer" : "Bargain"},
    { "question" : "A film which makes you laugh?.", "answer" : "Comedy"},
    { "question" : "A big shop usually on several floors where you can buy all kinds of things(two words)?.", "answer" : "department store"},
    { "question" : "People who appear in a film e.g. in crowd scenes, but who do not talk ?.", "answer" : "extra"},
    { "question" : "Somebody who really likes a sports team or film star, etc.?.", "answer" : "fan"},
    { "question" : "a written promise that a shop will repair something you buy?.", "answer" : "guarantee"},
    { "question" : "a brave person who people admire?.", "answer" : "hero"},
    { "question" : "A person who invents things?.", "answer" : "Inventor"},
    { "question" : "A person who is in change of a shop, restaurant or business, etc.?.", "answer" : "Manager"},
    { "question" : "The story of a film?.", "answer" : "plot"},
    { "question" : "A person who plays the violin?.", "answer" : "violinist"},
    { "question" : "A  film about cowboys?.", "answer" : "western"},
    { "question" : "Feeling, or acting in a manner consistent with, pessimism and despair.?.", "answer" : "doom and gloom"},
    { "question" : "Work with a lot of effort(2 words)?.", "answer" : "hard working"},
    { "question" : "Have problems making a decision?.", "answer" : "indecisive"},
    { "question" : "think differently or in a new way(4 words)?.", "answer" : "think outside the box"},
    { "question" : "Want to be more successful than others?.", "answer" : "competitive"},
    { "question" : "Want to be successful or powerful?.", "answer" : "ambitious"},
    { "question" : "Want to achieve something?.", "answer" : "motivated"},
    { "question" : "Person who does things which are dangerous(3 words)?.", "answer" : "a risk taker"},
    { "question" : "Person who has the qualities to manage a group of people(3 words)?.", "answer" : "a good leader"},
    { "question" : "Person who can express ideas or fealings clearly to others(3 words)?.", "answer" : "a good communicator"},
    { "question" : "What does irritated but accepting something?.", "answer" : "resigned to"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple was/were?.", "answer" : "be"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle been?.", "answer" : "be"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity be?.", "answer" : "was", "answer2" : "were"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle been?.", "answer" : "was", "answer2" : "were"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple was/were?.", "answer" : "been"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity be?.", "answer" : "been"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple beat?.", "answer" : "beat"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle beaten?.", "answer" : "beat"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity beat?.", "answer" : "beat" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle beaten?.", "answer" : "beat"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple beat?.", "answer" : "beaten"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity beat?.", "answer" : "beaten"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple became?.", "answer" : "become"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle become?.", "answer" : "become"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity become?.", "answer" : "became" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle become?.", "answer" : "become"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple became?.", "answer" : "become"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity become?.", "answer" : "become"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple began?.", "answer" : "begin"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle begun?.", "answer" : "begin"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity begin?.", "answer" : "began" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle begun?.", "answer" : "began"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple begin?.", "answer" : "begun"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity began?.", "answer" : "begun"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple began?.", "answer" : "bend"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle bent?.", "answer" : "bend"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity bend?.", "answer" : "bent" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle bent?.", "answer" : "bent"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple began?.", "answer" : "bent"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity bend?.", "answer" : "bent"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple bit?.", "answer" : "bite"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle bitten?.", "answer" : "bite"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity bite?.", "answer" : "bit" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle bitten?.", "answer" : "bit"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple bit?.", "answer" : "bitten"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity bite?.", "answer" : "bitten"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple blew?.", "answer" : "blow"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle blown?.", "answer" : "blow"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity blow?.", "answer" : "blew" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle blown?.", "answer" : "blew"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple blew?.", "answer" : "blown"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity blow?.", "answer" : "blown"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple broke?.", "answer" : "break"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle broken?.", "answer" : "break"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity break?.", "answer" : "broke" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle broken?.", "answer" : "broke"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple broke?.", "answer" : "broken"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity break?.", "answer" : "broken"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple broadcast?.", "answer" : "broadcast"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle broadcast?.", "answer" : "broadcast"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity broadcast?.", "answer" : "broadcast" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle broadcast?.", "answer" : "broadcast"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple broadcast?.", "answer" : "broadcast"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity broadcast?.", "answer" : "broadcast"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple brought?.", "answer" : "bring"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle brought?.", "answer" : "bring"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity bring?.", "answer" : "brought" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle brought?.", "answer" : "brought"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple brought?.", "answer" : "brought"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity bring?.", "answer" : "brought"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple built?.", "answer" : "build"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle built?.", "answer" : "build"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity build?.", "answer" : "built" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle built?.", "answer" : "built"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple built?.", "answer" : "built"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity build?.", "answer" : "built"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple burst?.", "answer" : "burst"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle burst?.", "answer" : "burst"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity burst?.", "answer" : "burst" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle burst?.", "answer" : "burst"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple burst?.", "answer" : "burst"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity burst?.", "answer" : "burst"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple bought?.", "answer" : "buy"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle bought?.", "answer" : "buy"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity buy?.", "answer" : "bought" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle bought?.", "answer" : "bought"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple bought?.", "answer" : "bought"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity buy?.", "answer" : "bought"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple caught?.", "answer" : "catch"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle caught?.", "answer" : "catch"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity catch?.", "answer" : "caught" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle caught?.", "answer" : "caught"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple caught?.", "answer" : "caught"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity catch?.", "answer" : "caught"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple chose?.", "answer" : "choose"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle chosen?.", "answer" : "choose"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity choose?.", "answer" : "chose" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle chosen?.", "answer" : "chose"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple chose?.", "answer" : "chosen"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity choose?.", "answer" : "chosen"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple came?.", "answer" : "come"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle come?.", "answer" : "come"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity come?.", "answer" : "came" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle come?.", "answer" : "came"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple came?.", "answer" : "come"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity come?.", "answer" : "come"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple cost?.", "answer" : "cost"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle cost?.", "answer" : "cost"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity cost?.", "answer" : "cost" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle cost?.", "answer" : "cost"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple cost?.", "answer" : "cost"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity cost?.", "answer" : "cost"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple crept?.", "answer" : "creep"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle crept?.", "answer" : "creep"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity creep?.", "answer" : "crept" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle crept?.", "answer" : "crept"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple crept?.", "answer" : "crept"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity creep?.", "answer" : "crept"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple cut?.", "answer" : "cut"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle cut?.", "answer" : "cut"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity cut?.", "answer" : "cut" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle cut?.", "answer" : "cut"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple cut?.", "answer" : "cut"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity cut?.", "answer" : "cut"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple dealt?.", "answer" : "deal"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle dealt?.", "answer" : "deal"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity deal?.", "answer" : "dealt" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle dealt?.", "answer" : "dealt"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple dealt?.", "answer" : "dealt"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity deal?.", "answer" : "dealt"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple dug?.", "answer" : "dig"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle dug?.", "answer" : "dig"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity dig?.", "answer" : "dug" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle dug?.", "answer" : "dug"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple dug?.", "answer" : "dug"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity dig?.", "answer" : "dug"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple did?.", "answer" : "do"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle done?.", "answer" : "do"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity do?.", "answer" : "did" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle done?.", "answer" : "did"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple did?.", "answer" : "done"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity do?.", "answer" : "done"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple drew?.", "answer" : "draw"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle drawn?.", "answer" : "draw"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity draw?.", "answer" : "drew" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle drawn?.", "answer" : "drew"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple drew?.", "answer" : "drawn"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity draw?.", "answer" : "drawn"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple dreamt?.", "answer" : "dream"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle dreamt?.", "answer" : "dream"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity dream?.", "answer" : "dreamt" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle dreamt?.", "answer" : "dreamt"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple dreamt?.", "answer" : "dreamt"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity dream?.", "answer" : "dreamt"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple drank?.", "answer" : "drink"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle drunk?.", "answer" : "drink"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity drink?.", "answer" : "drank" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle drunk?.", "answer" : "drank"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple drank?.", "answer" : "drunk"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity drink?.", "answer" : "drunk"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple drove?.", "answer" : "drive"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle driven?.", "answer" : "drive"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity drive?.", "answer" : "drove" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle driven?.", "answer" : "drove"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple drove?.", "answer" : "driven"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity drive?.", "answer" : "driven"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple ate?.", "answer" : "eat"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle eaten?.", "answer" : "eat"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity eat?.", "answer" : "ate" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle eaten?.", "answer" : "ate"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple ate?.", "answer" : "eaten"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity eat?.", "answer" : "eaten"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple fell?.", "answer" : "fall"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle fallen?.", "answer" : "fall"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity fall?.", "answer" : "fell" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle fallen?.", "answer" : "fell"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple fell?.", "answer" : "fallen"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity fall?.", "answer" : "fallen"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple fed?.", "answer" : "feed"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle fed?.", "answer" : "feed"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity feed?.", "answer" : "fed" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle fed?.", "answer" : "fed"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple fed?.", "answer" : "fed"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity feed?.", "answer" : "fed"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple felt?.", "answer" : "feel"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle felt?.", "answer" : "feel"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity feel?.", "answer" : "felt" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle felt?.", "answer" : "felt"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple felt?.", "answer" : "felt"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity feel?.", "answer" : "felt"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple fought?.", "answer" : "fight"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle fought?.", "answer" : "fight"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity fight?.", "answer" : "fought" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle fought?.", "answer" : "fought"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple fought?.", "answer" : "fought"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity fight?.", "answer" : "fought"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple found?.", "answer" : "find"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle found?.", "answer" : "find"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity find?.", "answer" : "found" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle found?.", "answer" : "found"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple found?.", "answer" : "found"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity find?.", "answer" : "found"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple fled?.", "answer" : "flee"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle fled?.", "answer" : "flee"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity flee?.", "answer" : "fled" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle fled?.", "answer" : "fled"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple fled?.", "answer" : "fled"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity flee?.", "answer" : "fled"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple flew?.", "answer" : "fly"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle flown?.", "answer" : "fly"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity fly?.", "answer" : "flew" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle flown?.", "answer" : "flew"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple flew?.", "answer" : "flown"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity fly?.", "answer" : "flown"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple forbade?.", "answer" : "forbid"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle forbidden?.", "answer" : "forbid"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity forbid?.", "answer" : "forbade" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle forbidden?.", "answer" : "forbade"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple forbade?.", "answer" : "forbidden"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity forbid?.", "answer" : "forbidden"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple forgot?.", "answer" : "forget"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle forgotten?.", "answer" : "forget"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity forget?.", "answer" : "forgot" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle forgotten?.", "answer" : "forgot"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple forgot?.", "answer" : "forgotten"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity forget?.", "answer" : "forgotten"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple forgave?.", "answer" : "forgive"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle forgiven?.", "answer" : "forgive"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity forgive?.", "answer" : "forgave" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle forgiven?.", "answer" : "forgave"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple forgave?.", "answer" : "forgiven"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity forgive?.", "answer" : "forgiven"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple froze?.", "answer" : "freeze"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle frozen?.", "answer" : "freeze"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity freeze?.", "answer" : "froze" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle frozen?.", "answer" : "froze"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple froze?.", "answer" : "frozen"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity freeze?.", "answer" : "frozen"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple got?.", "answer" : "get"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle gotten?.", "answer" : "get"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity get?.", "answer" : "got" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle gotten?.", "answer" : "got"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple got?.", "answer" : "gotten"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity get?.", "answer" : "gotten"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple gave?.", "answer" : "give"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle given?.", "answer" : "give"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity give?.", "answer" : "gave" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle given?.", "answer" : "gave"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple gave?.", "answer" : "given"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity give?.", "answer" : "given"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple went?.", "answer" : "go"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle gone?.", "answer" : "go"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity go?.", "answer" : "went" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle gone?.", "answer" : "went"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple went?.", "answer" : "gone"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity go?.", "answer" : "gone"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple grew?.", "answer" : "grow"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle grown?.", "answer" : "grow"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity grow?.", "answer" : "grew" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle grown?.", "answer" : "grew"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple grew?.", "answer" : "grown"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity grow?.", "answer" : "grown"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple hung?.", "answer" : "hang"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle hung?.", "answer" : "hang"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity hang?.", "answer" : "hung" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle hung?.", "answer" : "hung"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple hung?.", "answer" : "hung"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity hang?.", "answer" : "hung"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple had?.", "answer" : "have"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle had?.", "answer" : "have"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity have?.", "answer" : "had" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle had?.", "answer" : "had"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple had?.", "answer" : "had"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity have?.", "answer" : "had"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple heard?.", "answer" : "hear"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle heard?.", "answer" : "hear"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity hear?.", "answer" : "heard" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle heard?.", "answer" : "heard"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple heard?.", "answer" : "heard"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity hear?.", "answer" : "heard"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple hid?.", "answer" : "hide"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle hidden?.", "answer" : "hide"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity hide?.", "answer" : "hid" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle hidden?.", "answer" : "hid"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple hid?.", "answer" : "hidden"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity hide?.", "answer" : "hidden"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple hit?.", "answer" : "hit"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle hit?.", "answer" : "hit"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity hit?.", "answer" : "hit" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle hit?.", "answer" : "hit"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple hit?.", "answer" : "hit"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity hit?.", "answer" : "hit"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple held?.", "answer" : "hold"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle held?.", "answer" : "hold"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity hold?.", "answer" : "held" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle held?.", "answer" : "held"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple held?.", "answer" : "held"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity hold?.", "answer" : "held"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple hurt?.", "answer" : "hurt"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle hurt?.", "answer" : "hurt"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity hurt?.", "answer" : "hurt" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle hurt?.", "answer" : "hurt"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple hurt?.", "answer" : "hurt"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity hurt?.", "answer" : "hurt"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple kept?.", "answer" : "keep"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle kept?.", "answer" : "keep"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity keep?.", "answer" : "kept" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle kept?.", "answer" : "kept"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple kept?.", "answer" : "kept"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity keep?.", "answer" : "kept"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple knelt?.", "answer" : "kneel"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle knelt?.", "answer" : "kneel"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity kneel?.", "answer" : "knelt" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle knelt?.", "answer" : "knelt"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple knelt?.", "answer" : "knelt"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity kneel?.", "answer" : "knelt"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple knitted?.", "answer" : "knit"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle knitted?.", "answer" : "knit"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity knit?.", "answer" : "knitted" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle knitted?.", "answer" : "knitted"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple knitted?.", "answer" : "knitted"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity knit?.", "answer" : "knitted"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple knew?.", "answer" : "know"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle known?.", "answer" : "know"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity know?.", "answer" : "knew" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle known?.", "answer" : "knew"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple knew?.", "answer" : "known"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity know?.", "answer" : "known"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple laid?.", "answer" : "lay"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle laid?.", "answer" : "lay"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity lay?.", "answer" : "laid" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle laid?.", "answer" : "laid"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple laid?.", "answer" : "laid"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity lay?.", "answer" : "laid"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple led?.", "answer" : "lead"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle led?.", "answer" : "lead"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity lead?.", "answer" : "led" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle led?.", "answer" : "led"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple led?.", "answer" : "led"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity lead?.", "answer" : "led"},



    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple leaned?.", "answer" : "lean"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle leaned?.", "answer" : "lean"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity lean?.", "answer" : "leaned" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle leaned?.", "answer" : "leaned"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple leaned?.", "answer" : "leaned"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity lean?.", "answer" : "leaned"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple left?.", "answer" : "leave"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle left?.", "answer" : "leave"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity leave?.", "answer" : "left" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle left?.", "answer" : "left"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple left?.", "answer" : "left"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity leave?.", "answer" : "left"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple lent?.", "answer" : "lend"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle lent?.", "answer" : "lend"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity lend?.", "answer" : "lent" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle lent?.", "answer" : "lent"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple lent?.", "answer" : "lent"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity lend?.", "answer" : "lent"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple let?.", "answer" : "let"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle let?.", "answer" : "let"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity let?.", "answer" : "let" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle let?.", "answer" : "let"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple let?.", "answer" : "let"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity let?.", "answer" : "let"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple learned?.", "answer" : "learn"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle learned?.", "answer" : "learn"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity learn?.", "answer" : "learned" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle learned?.", "answer" : "learned"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple learned?.", "answer" : "learned"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity learn?.", "answer" : "learned"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple lay?.", "answer" : "lie"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle lain?.", "answer" : "lie"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity lie?.", "answer" : "lay" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle lain?.", "answer" : "lay"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple lay?.", "answer" : "lain"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity lie?.", "answer" : "lain"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple lied?.", "answer" : "lie"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle lied?.", "answer" : "lie"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity lie?.", "answer" : "lied" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle lied?.", "answer" : "lied"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple lied?.", "answer" : "lied"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity lie?.", "answer" : "lied"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple lit?.", "answer" : "light"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle lit?.", "answer" : "light"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity light?.", "answer" : "lit" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle lit?.", "answer" : "lit"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple lit?.", "answer" : "lit"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity light?.", "answer" : "lit"},


    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple lost?.", "answer" : "lose"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle lost?.", "answer" : "lose"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity lose?.", "answer" : "lost" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle lost?.", "answer" : "lost"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple lost?.", "answer" : "lost"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity lose?.", "answer" : "lost"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple made?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle made?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity make?.", "answer" : "made" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle made?.", "answer" : "made"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple made?.", "answer" : "made"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity make?.", "answer" : "made"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple meant?.", "answer" : "mean"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle meant?.", "answer" : "mean"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity mean?.", "answer" : "meant" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle meant?.", "answer" : "meant"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple meant?.", "answer" : "meant"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity mean?.", "answer" : "meant"},


    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple met?.", "answer" : "meet"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle met?.", "answer" : "meet"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity meet?.", "answer" : "met" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle met?.", "answer" : "met"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple met?.", "answer" : "met"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity meet?.", "answer" : "met"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple paid?.", "answer" : "pay"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle paid?.", "answer" : "pay"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity pay?.", "answer" : "paid" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle paid?.", "answer" : "paid"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple paid?.", "answer" : "paid"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity pay?.", "answer" : "paid"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple put?.", "answer" : "put"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle put?.", "answer" : "put"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity put?.", "answer" : "put" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle put?.", "answer" : "put"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple put?.", "answer" : "put"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity put?.", "answer" : "put"},


    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple read?.", "answer" : "read"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle read?.", "answer" : "read"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity read?.", "answer" : "read" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle read?.", "answer" : "read"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple read?.", "answer" : "read"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity read?.", "answer" : "read"},


    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple set?.", "answer" : "set"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle set?.", "answer" : "set"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity set?.", "answer" : "set" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle set?.", "answer" : "set"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple set?.", "answer" : "set"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity set?.", "answer" : "set"},


    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple shut?.", "answer" : "shut"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle shut?.", "answer" : "shut"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity shut?.", "answer" : "shut" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle shut?.", "answer" : "shut"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple shut?.", "answer" : "shut"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity shut?.", "answer" : "shut"},

    { "question" : "What is the adverb of beautiful?.", "answer" : "beautifully", "example" : "Andres plays the cello beautifully"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of beautifully?.", "answer" : "beautiful"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of day?.", "answer" : "daily",  "example" : "The museum is open daily from nine to five"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of daily?.", "answer" : "day"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of happy?.", "answer" : "happily" , "example" : "The children were playing happily on the beach"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of happily?.", "answer" : "happy"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of probable?.", "answer" : "probably", "example" : "I wonder why our friends have not arrived . They have probably been delayed by the traffic"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of probably?.", "answer" : "probable"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of quiet?.", "answer" : "quietly", "example" : "Andres closed the door quietly so that he would not wake the baby up"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of quietly?.", "answer" : "quiet"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of brilliant?.", "answer" : "brilliantly"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of brilliantly?.", "answer" : "brilliant"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of careful?.", "answer" : "carefully"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of carefully?.", "answer" : "careful"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of effective?.", "answer" : "effectively"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of effectively?.", "answer" : "effective"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of efficient?.", "answer" : "efficiently"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of efficiently?.", "answer" : "efficient"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of excited?.", "answer" : "excitedly"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of excitedly?.", "answer" : "excited"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of hurried?.", "answer" : "hurriedly"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of hurriedly?.", "answer" : "hurried"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of occasional?.", "answer" : "occasionally"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of occasionally?.", "answer" : "occasional"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of shy?.", "answer" : "shyly"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of shyly?.", "answer" : "shy"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of truthful?.", "answer" : "truthfully"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of truthfully?.", "answer" : "truthful"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of undoubted?.", "answer" : "undoubtedly"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of undoubtedly?.", "answer" : "undoubted"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of unexpected?.", "answer" : "unexpectedly"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of unexpectedly?.", "answer" : "unexpected"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of wholehearted?.", "answer" : "wholeheartedly"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of wholeheartedly?.", "answer" : "wholehearted"},
    { "question" : "In writing  what is the impersonal structure of Of course?.", "answer" : "it goes without saying that"},
    { "question" : "In writing  what is the impersonal structure of In my opinion?.", "answer" : "it does not seem unreasonable to suggest that"},
    { "question" : "In writing  what is the impersonal structure of In my opinion?.", "answer" : "it does not seem unreasonable to suggest that"},


    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the noun length?.", "answer" : "lengthily"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the noun length?.", "answer" : "lengthen"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun length?.", "answer" : "long"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adverb lengthily?.", "answer" : "length"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the adverb lengthily?.", "answer" : "lengthen"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of adverb noun lengthily?.", "answer" : "long"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the verb lengthen?.", "answer" : "length"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the verb lengthen?.", "answer" : "lengthily"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of verb noun lengthen?.", "answer" : "long"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective long?.", "answer" : "length"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the adjective long?.", "answer" : "lengthily"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of adjective noun long?.", "answer" : "lengthen"},



    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the noun weakness?.", "answer" : "weakly"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the noun weakness?.", "answer" : "weaken"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun weakness?.", "answer" : "week"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adverb weakly?.", "answer" : "weakness"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the adverb weakly?.", "answer" : "weaken"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of adverb noun weakly?.", "answer" : "week"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the verb weaken?.", "answer" : "weakness"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the verb weaken?.", "answer" : "weakly"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of verb noun weaken?.", "answer" : "week"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective week?.", "answer" : "weakness"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the adjective week?.", "answer" : "weakly"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of adjective noun week?.", "answer" : "weaken"},


    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the noun depth?.", "answer" : "deeply"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the noun depth?.", "answer" : "deepen"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun depth?.", "answer" : "deep"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adverb deeply?.", "answer" : "depth"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the adverb deeply?.", "answer" : "deepen"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of adverb noun deeply?.", "answer" : "deep"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the verb deepen?.", "answer" : "depth"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the verb deepen?.", "answer" : "deeply"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of verb noun deepen?.", "answer" : "deep"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective deep?.", "answer" : "depth"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the adjective deep?.", "answer" : "deeply"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of adjective noun deep?.", "answer" : "deepen"},



    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the noun strength?.", "answer" : "strongly"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the noun strength?.", "answer" : "strengthener"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun strength?.", "answer" : "strong"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adverb strongly?.", "answer" : "strength"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the adverb strongly?.", "answer" : "strengthener"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of adverb noun strongly?.", "answer" : "strong"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the verb strengthener?.", "answer" : "strength"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the verb strengthener?.", "answer" : "strongly"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of verb noun strengthener?.", "answer" : "strong"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective strong?.", "answer" : "strength"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the adjective strong?.", "answer" : "strongly"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of adjective noun strong?.", "answer" : "strengthener"},



    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the noun width?.", "answer" : "widely"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the noun width?.", "answer" : "widen"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun width?.", "answer" : "wide"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adverb widely?.", "answer" : "width"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the adverb widely?.", "answer" : "widen"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of adverb noun widely?.", "answer" : "wide"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the verb widen?.", "answer" : "width"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the verb widen?.", "answer" : "widely"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of verb noun widen?.", "answer" : "wide"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective wide?.", "answer" : "width"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the adjective wide?.", "answer" : "widely"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of adjective noun wide?.", "answer" : "widen"},



    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the noun shortage?.", "answer" : "shortly"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the noun shortage?.", "answer" : "shorten"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun shortage?.", "answer" : "short"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adverb shortly?.", "answer" : "shortage"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the adverb shortly?.", "answer" : "shorten"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of adverb noun shortly?.", "answer" : "short"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the verb shorten?.", "answer" : "shortage"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the verb shorten?.", "answer" : "shortly"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of verb noun shorten?.", "answer" : "short"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective short?.", "answer" : "shortage"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the adjective short?.", "answer" : "shortly"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of adjective noun short?.", "answer" : "shorten"},


    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the noun warmth?.", "answer" : "warmly"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the noun warmth?.", "answer" : "warm"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of the noun warmth?.", "answer" : "warm"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adverb warmly?.", "answer" : "warmth"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of the adverb warmly?.", "answer" : "warm"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of adverb noun warmly?.", "answer" : "warm"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the verb warm?.", "answer" : "warmth"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the verb warm?.", "answer" : "warmly"},
    { "question" : "What is the adjective of verb noun warm?.", "answer" : "warm"},

    { "question" : "What is the noun of the adjective warm?.", "answer" : "warmth"},
    { "question" : "What is the adverb of the adjective warm?.", "answer" : "warmly"},
    { "question" : "What is the verb of adjective noun warm?.", "answer" : "warm"},



    { "question" : "a holiday where you purchase the travel and accommodation together?.", "answer" : "package holiday", "answer2" : "all-in package"},
    { "question" : "an extremely beautiful view?.", "answer" : "breathtaking view"},
    { "question" : "a cheaper form of flying than a scheduled flight?.", "answer" : "charter-flight"},
    { "question" : "the place at the airport where you register for your flight and deposit your luggage?.", "answer" : "check-in desk"},
    { "question" : "where you wait for your flight to be called?.", "answer" : "departure lounge"},
    { "question" : "somewhere a long way away?.", "answer" : "far-off destination"},
    { "question" : "to take a holiday to escape a busy or stressful lifestyle?.", "answer" : "to get away from it all"},
    { "question" : "an organised group shown around a place of interest by an expert?.", "answer" : "guided tour"},
    { "question" : "a glossy publication with details of holiday packages?.", "answer" : "holiday brochure"},
    { "question" : "where you go for a holiday?.", "answer" : "holiday destination"},
    { "question" : "a special holiday that you are unlikely to repeat?.", "answer" : "holiday of a lifetime"},
    { "question" : "a place where lots of people go for a holiday?.", "answer" : "holiday resort"},
    { "question" : "crowds of tourists?.", "answer" : "hordes of tourists"},
    { "question" : "objects produced locally?.", "answer" : "local crafts"},
    { "question" : "an extended weekend holiday including Friday or Monday?.", "answer" : "long weekend"},
    { "question" : "outside of the main holiday period?.", "answer" : "out of season"},
    { "question" : "very pretty village?.", "answer" : "picturesque village"},
    { "question" : "the place where your passport is checked?.", "answer" : "passport control"},
    { "question" : "sites of interest to tourists?.", "answer" : "places of interest"},
    { "question" : "a holiday, often in Africa, to observe wild animals?.", "answer" : "wildlife safari"},
    { "question" : "a holiday where you supply your own food?.", "answer" : "self-catering"},
    { "question" : "a short holiday?.", "answer" : "short break"},
    { "question" : "to look around the tourist sites?.", "answer" : "to go sightseeing"},
    { "question" : "extremely beautiful countryside?.", "answer" : "stunning landscape"},
    { "question" : "a shop that specialises in booking holidays?.", "answer" : "travel agent"},
    { "question" : "somewhere where too many tourists go?.", "answer" : "tourist trap"},
    { "question" : "to end a romantic relationship?.", "answer" : "youth hostel"},


    { "question" : "a cheap form of accommodation?.", "answer" : "to break up"},
    { "question" : "to become less close to someone?.", "answer" : "to drift apart"},
    { "question" : "to like spending time with someone?.", "answer" : "to enjoy someone’s company"},
    { "question" : "to like spending time with someone?.", "answer" : "to enjoy someone’s company"},
    { "question" : "to fall in love?.", "answer" : "to fall for"},
    { "question" : "to start to love someone a lot?.", "answer" : "to fall head over heels in love"},
    { "question" : "to fall out with?.", "answer" : "to have a disagreement and stop being friends"},
    { "question" : "to get on like a house on fire?.", "answer" : "to like someone’s company very much indeed"},
    { "question" : "to understand someone and enjoy similar interests?.", "answer" : "to get on well with"},
    { "question" : "to begin to know someone?.", "answer" : "to get to know"},
    { "question" : "to have known someone for a long time?.", "answer" : "to go back years"},
    { "question" : "to share similar interests?.", "answer" : "to have a lot in common"},
    { "question" : "to have good and bad times?.", "answer" : "to have ups and downs"},
    { "question" : "a good, positive relationship?.", "answer" : "a healthy relationship"},
    { "question" : "to quickly become good friends with?.", "answer" : "to hit it off"},
    { "question" : "to be romantically involved with someone?.", "answer" : "to be in a relationship"},
    { "question" : "to not be romantically involved?.", "answer" : "to be just good friends"},
    { "question" : "to keep in touch with?.", "answer" : "to keep in contact with"},
    { "question" : "to not see or hear from someone any longer?.", "answer" : "to lose touch with"},
    { "question" : "to fall in love immediately you meet someone?.", "answer" : "love at first sight"},
    { "question" : "to ask someone to marry you?.", "answer" : "to pop the question"},
    { "question" : "to agree on a subject?.", "answer" : "to see eye to eye"},
    { "question" : "to give up the single life and start a family?.", "answer" : "to settle down"},
    { "question" : "to tie the knot?.", "answer" : "to get married"},
    { "question" : "to be well matched?.", "answer" : "to be similar to"},
    { "question" : "to try to maintain a positive relationship with someone?.", "answer" : "to work at a relationship"},


    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple rode?.", "answer" : "ride"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle ridden?.", "answer" : "ride"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity ride?.", "answer" : "rode" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle ridden?.", "answer" : "rode"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple rode?.", "answer" : "ridden"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity ride?.", "answer" : "ridden"},


    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple rang?.", "answer" : "ring"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle rung?.", "answer" : "ring"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity ring?.", "answer" : "rang" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle rung?.", "answer" : "rang"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple rang?.", "answer" : "rung"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity ring?.", "answer" : "rung"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple rose?.", "answer" : "rise"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle risen?.", "answer" : "rise"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity rise?.", "answer" : "rose" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle risen?.", "answer" : "rose"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple rose?.", "answer" : "risen"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity rise?.", "answer" : "risen"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple ran?.", "answer" : "run"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle run?.", "answer" : "run"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity run?.", "answer" : "ran" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle run?.", "answer" : "ran"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple ran?.", "answer" : "run"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity run?.", "answer" : "run"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple said?.", "answer" : "say"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle said?.", "answer" : "say"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity say?.", "answer" : "said" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle said?.", "answer" : "said"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple said?.", "answer" : "said"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity say?.", "answer" : "said"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple saw?.", "answer" : "see"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle seen?.", "answer" : "see"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity see?.", "answer" : "saw" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle seen?.", "answer" : "saw"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple saw?.", "answer" : "seen"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity see?.", "answer" : "seen"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple sought?.", "answer" : "seek"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle sought?.", "answer" : "seek"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity seek?.", "answer" : "sought" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle sought?.", "answer" : "sought"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple sought?.", "answer" : "sought"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity seek?.", "answer" : "sought"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple sold?.", "answer" : "sell"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle sold?.", "answer" : "sell"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity sell?.", "answer" : "sold" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle sold?.", "answer" : "sold"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple sold?.", "answer" : "sold"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity sell?.", "answer" : "sold"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple sent?.", "answer" : "send"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle sent?.", "answer" : "send"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity send?.", "answer" : "sent" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle sent?.", "answer" : "sent"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple sent?.", "answer" : "sent"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity send?.", "answer" : "sent"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple sewed?.", "answer" : "sew"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle sewn?.", "answer" : "sew"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity sew?.", "answer" : "sewed" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle sewn?.", "answer" : "sewed"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple sewed?.", "answer" : "sewn"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity sew?.", "answer" : "sewn"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple shook?.", "answer" : "shake"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle shaken?.", "answer" : "shake"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity shake?.", "answer" : "shook" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle shaken?.", "answer" : "shook"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple shook?.", "answer" : "shaken"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity shake?.", "answer" : "shaken"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple shaved?.", "answer" : "shave"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle shaven?.", "answer" : "shave"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity shave?.", "answer" : "shaved" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle shaven?.", "answer" : "shaved"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple shaved?.", "answer" : "shaven"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity shave?.", "answer" : "shaven"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple shone?.", "answer" : "shine"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle shone?.", "answer" : "shine"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity shine?.", "answer" : "shone" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle shone?.", "answer" : "shone"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple shone?.", "answer" : "shone"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity shine?.", "answer" : "shone"},


    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple shot?.", "answer" : "shoot"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle shot?.", "answer" : "shoot"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity shoot?.", "answer" : "shot" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle shot?.", "answer" : "shot"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple shot?.", "answer" : "shot"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity shoot?.", "answer" : "shot"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple sat?.", "answer" : "sit"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle sat?.", "answer" : "sit"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity sit?.", "answer" : "sat" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle sat?.", "answer" : "sat"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple sat?.", "answer" : "sat"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity sit?.", "answer" : "sat"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple slept?.", "answer" : "sleep"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle slept?.", "answer" : "sleep"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity sleep?.", "answer" : "slept" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle slept?.", "answer" : "slept"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple slept?.", "answer" : "slept"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity sleep?.", "answer" : "slept"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple spent?.", "answer" : "spend"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle spent?.", "answer" : "spend"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity spend?.", "answer" : "spent" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle spent?.", "answer" : "spent"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple spent?.", "answer" : "spent"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity spend?.", "answer" : "spent"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple stood?.", "answer" : "stand"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle stood?.", "answer" : "stand"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity stand?.", "answer" : "stood" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle stood?.", "answer" : "stood"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple stood?.", "answer" : "stood"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity stand?.", "answer" : "stood"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple slid?.", "answer" : "slide"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle slid?.", "answer" : "slide"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity slide?.", "answer" : "slid" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle slid?.", "answer" : "slid"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple slid?.", "answer" : "slid"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity slide?.", "answer" : "slid"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple split?.", "answer" : "split"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle split?.", "answer" : "split"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity split?.", "answer" : "split" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle split?.", "answer" : "split"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple split?.", "answer" : "split"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity split?.", "answer" : "split"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple spread?.", "answer" : "spread"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle spread?.", "answer" : "spread"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity spread?.", "answer" : "spread" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle spread?.", "answer" : "spread"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple spread?.", "answer" : "spread"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity spread?.", "answer" : "spread"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple spat?.", "answer" : "spit"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle spat?.", "answer" : "spit"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity spit?.", "answer" : "spat" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle spat?.", "answer" : "spat"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple spat?.", "answer" : "spat"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity spit?.", "answer" : "spat"},


    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple struck?.", "answer" : "strike"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle struck?.", "answer" : "strike"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity strike?.", "answer" : "struck" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle spat?.", "answer" : "struck"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple spat?.", "answer" : "struck"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity strike?.", "answer" : "struck"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple taught?.", "answer" : "teach"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle taught?.", "answer" : "teach"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity teach?.", "answer" : "taught" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle taught?.", "answer" : "taught"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple taught?.", "answer" : "taught"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity teach?.", "answer" : "taught"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple told?.", "answer" : "tell"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle told?.", "answer" : "tell"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity tell?.", "answer" : "told" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle taught?.", "answer" : "told"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple taught?.", "answer" : "told"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity tell?.", "answer" : "told"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple thought?.", "answer" : "think"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle thought?.", "answer" : "think"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity think?.", "answer" : "thought" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle taught?.", "answer" : "thought"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple taught?.", "answer" : "thought"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity think?.", "answer" : "thought"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple showed?.", "answer" : "show"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle shown?.", "answer" : "show"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity show?.", "answer" : "showed" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle shown?.", "answer" : "showed"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple showed?.", "answer" : "shown"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity show?.", "answer" : "shown"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple shrank?.", "answer" : "shrink"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle shrunk?.", "answer" : "shrink"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity shrink?.", "answer" : "shrank" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle shrunk?.", "answer" : "shrank"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple shrank?.", "answer" : "shrunk"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity shrink?.", "answer" : "shrunk"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple sang?.", "answer" : "sing"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle sung?.", "answer" : "sing"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity sing?.", "answer" : "sang" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle sung?.", "answer" : "sang"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple sang?.", "answer" : "sung"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity sing?.", "answer" : "sung"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple sank?.", "answer" : "sink"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle sunk?.", "answer" : "sink"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity sink?.", "answer" : "sank" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle sunk?.", "answer" : "sank"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple sank?.", "answer" : "sunk"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity sink?.", "answer" : "sunk"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple spoke?.", "answer" : "speak"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle spoken?.", "answer" : "speak"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity speak?.", "answer" : "spoke" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle spoken?.", "answer" : "spoke"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple spoke?.", "answer" : "spoken"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity speak?.", "answer" : "spoken"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple sprang?.", "answer" : "spring"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle sprung?.", "answer" : "spring"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity spring?.", "answer" : "sprang" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle sprung?.", "answer" : "sprang"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple sprang?.", "answer" : "sprung"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity spring?.", "answer" : "sprung"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple sprang?.", "answer" : "spring"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle sprung?.", "answer" : "spring"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity spring?.", "answer" : "sprang" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle sprung?.", "answer" : "sprang"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple sprang?.", "answer" : "sprung"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity spring?.", "answer" : "sprung"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple stole?.", "answer" : "steal"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle stolen?.", "answer" : "steal"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity steal?.", "answer" : "stole" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle stolen?.", "answer" : "stole"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple stole?.", "answer" : "stolen"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity steal?.", "answer" : "stolen"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple stuck?.", "answer" : "stick"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle stuck?.", "answer" : "stick"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity stick?.", "answer" : "stuck" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle stuck?.", "answer" : "stuck"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple stuck?.", "answer" : "stuck"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity stick?.", "answer" : "stuck"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple stung?.", "answer" : "sting"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle stung?.", "answer" : "sting"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity sting?.", "answer" : "stung" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle stung?.", "answer" : "stung"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple stung?.", "answer" : "stung"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity sting?.", "answer" : "stung"},


    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple stank?.", "answer" : "stink"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle stunk?.", "answer" : "stink"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity stink?.", "answer" : "stank" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle stunk?.", "answer" : "stank"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple stank?.", "answer" : "stunk"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity stink?.", "answer" : "stunk"},


    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple tore?.", "answer" : "tear"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle torn?.", "answer" : "tear"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity tear?.", "answer" : "tore" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle torn?.", "answer" : "tore"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple tore?.", "answer" : "torn"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity tear?.", "answer" : "torn"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple swam?.", "answer" : "swim"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle swum?.", "answer" : "swim"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity swim?.", "answer" : "swam" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle swum?.", "answer" : "swam"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple swam?.", "answer" : "swum"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity swim?.", "answer" : "swum"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple swore?.", "answer" : "swear"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle sworn?.", "answer" : "swear"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity swear?.", "answer" : "swore" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle sworn?.", "answer" : "swore"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple swore?.", "answer" : "sworn"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity swear?.", "answer" : "sworn"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple swept?.", "answer" : "sweep"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle swept?.", "answer" : "sweep"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity sweep?.", "answer" : "swept" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle swept?.", "answer" : "swept"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple swept?.", "answer" : "swept"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity sweep?.", "answer" : "swept"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple swung?.", "answer" : "swing"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle swung?.", "answer" : "swing"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity swing?.", "answer" : "swung" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle swung?.", "answer" : "swung"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple swung?.", "answer" : "swung"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity swing?.", "answer" : "swung"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple took?.", "answer" : "take"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle taken?.", "answer" : "take"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity take?.", "answer" : "took" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle taken?.", "answer" : "took"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple took?.", "answer" : "taken"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity take?.", "answer" : "taken"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple wore?.", "answer" : "wear"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle worn?.", "answer" : "wear"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity wear?.", "answer" : "wore" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle worn?.", "answer" : "wore"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple wore?.", "answer" : "worn"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity wear?.", "answer" : "worn"},


    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple threw?.", "answer" : "throw"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle thrown?.", "answer" : "throw"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity throw?.", "answer" : "threw" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle thrown?.", "answer" : "threw"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple threw?.", "answer" : "thrown"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity throw?.", "answer" : "thrown"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple understood?.", "answer" : "understand"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle understood?.", "answer" : "understand"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity understand?.", "answer" : "understood" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle understood?.", "answer" : "understood"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple understood?.", "answer" : "understood"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity understand?.", "answer" : "understood"},


    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple woke?.", "answer" : "wake"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle woken?.", "answer" : "wake"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity wake?.", "answer" : "woke" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle woken?.", "answer" : "woke"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple woke?.", "answer" : "woken"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity wake?.", "answer" : "woken"},


    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple won?.", "answer" : "win"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle won?.", "answer" : "win"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity win?.", "answer" : "won" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle won?.", "answer" : "won"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple won?.", "answer" : "won"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity win?.", "answer" : "won"},


    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple wept?.", "answer" : "weep"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle wept?.", "answer" : "weep"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity weep?.", "answer" : "wept" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle won?.", "answer" : "wept"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple won?.", "answer" : "wept"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity weep?.", "answer" : "wept"},

    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past simple wrote?.", "answer" : "write"},
    { "question" : "What does the infinity of the past participle written?.", "answer" : "write"},
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the infinity write?.", "answer" : "wrote" },
    { "question" : "What does the past simple of the past participle written?.", "answer" : "wrote"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the past simple wrote?.", "answer" : "written"},
    { "question" : "What does the past participle of the  infinity write?.", "answer" : "written"},


    { "question" : "(Make or do)  I ____ the shopping?.", "answer" : "do"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  I ____ the washing up?.", "answer" : "do"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  I ____ the housework?.", "answer" : "do"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  I ____ some housework?.", "answer" : "do"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  I ____ the dishes?.", "answer" : "do"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  I ____ the cooking?.", "answer" : "do"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  I ____ a full time job?.", "answer" : "do"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ your best?.", "answer" : "do"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ business?.", "answer" : "do"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ a course?.", "answer" : "do"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ exercise?.", "answer" : "do"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ someone a favour?.", "answer" : "do"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ homework?.", "answer" : "do"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ sport?.", "answer" : "do"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ work?.", "answer" : "do"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ a crossword?.", "answer" : "do"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ research?.", "answer" : "do"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ a job?.", "answer" : "do"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ an English course?.", "answer" : "do"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ an appointment?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ the bed?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ a decision?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ an effort?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ an excuse?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ friends?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ fun of someone?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ a fuss?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ a mess?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ money?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ a noise?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ a phone call?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ a photocopy?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ a plan?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ progress?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ a promise?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ a suggestion?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ a trip?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ a notes?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ a mistake?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ progress?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ time?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ fun?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  ____ coffee?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  We need to ___ a decision about which candidate should get the job?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  He is used to ___ a lot of business trips?.", "answer" : "making"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  She is given me so much homework to ___ I'll never get through it?.", "answer" : "do"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  You're doing very well! You've ___ very good progress?.", "answer" : "made"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  If you practised more you wouldn't ___ so many mistakes?.", "answer" : "make"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  Can you ___ me a favour and drop me off at the bank?.", "answer" : "do"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  I've just tidied up! Who's ___ all this mess?.", "answer" : "made"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  It's not easy ___ business with him when he's so unreliable?.", "answer" : "doing"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  Keeping fit isn't easy unless you ___ an effort?.", "answer" : "do"},
    { "question" : "(Make or do)  Ahmed said he'd like to ___ a course in Excel?.", "answer" : "do"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ a role?.", "answer" : "play"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ cards?.", "answer" : "play"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ basketball?.", "answer" : "play"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ the piano?.", "answer" : "play"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ tennis?.", "answer" : "play"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ football?.", "answer" : "play"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ with someone feelings?.", "answer" : "play"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ a living?.", "answer" : "earn"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ money?.", "answer" : "earn"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ respect?.", "answer" : "earn"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ salary?.", "answer" : "earn"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ a prize?.", "answer" : "win"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ a race?.", "answer" : "win"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ a tournament?.", "answer" : "win"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ a match?.", "answer" : "win"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ the support of(e.g someone/his fans)?.", "answer" : "win"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ shopping?.", "answer" : "go"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ riding?.", "answer" : "go"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ swimming?.", "answer" : "go"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ skiing?.", "answer" : "go"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ cycling?.", "answer" : "go"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ sailing?.", "answer" : "go"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ fishing?.", "answer" : "go"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ climbing?.", "answer" : "go"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ an opponent?.", "answer" : "beat"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ the record?.", "answer" : "beat"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ a carpet(means : clean carpets from the dust)?.", "answer" : "beat"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ traffic(means: avoid the traffic)?.", "answer" : "beat"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ a fish?.", "answer" : "catch"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ the ball?.", "answer" : "catch"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ a fly?.", "answer" : "catch"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ a cold?.", "answer" : "catch"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ a train?.", "answer" : "catch"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ a bus?.", "answer" : "catch"},
    { "question" : "(Collocation)  ___ glimpse of someone or something(means : see something for a brief time)?.", "answer" : "catch"},
    { "question" : "The british spelling of center(American English)?.", "answer" : "centre"},
    { "question" : "The british spelling of theater(American English)?.", "answer" : "theatre"},
    { "question" : "The british spelling of meter(American English)?.", "answer" : "metre"},
    { "question" : "The british spelling of practice(American English) like noun?.", "answer" : "practice"},
    { "question" : "The british spelling of practice(American English) like verb?.", "answer" : "practise"},
    { "question" : "The british spelling of licence(American English) like noun?.", "answer" : "licence"},
    { "question" : "The british spelling of licence(American English) like verb?.", "answer" : "license"},
    { "question" : "The british spelling of behavior(American English)?.", "answer" : "behaviour"},
    { "question" : "The british spelling of color(American English)?.", "answer" : "colour"},
    { "question" : "The british spelling of humor(American English)?.", "answer" : "humour"},
    { "question" : "The british spelling of labor(American English)?.", "answer" : "labour"},
    { "question" : "The british spelling of neighbor(American English)?.", "answer" : "neighbour"},
    { "question" : "The british spelling of rumor(American English)?.", "answer" : "rumour"},
    { "question" : "The british spelling of check(American English)?.", "answer" : "cheque"},
    { "question" : "The british spelling of program(American English)?.", "answer" : "programme"},
    { "question" : "The british spelling of What (color) is your new car?.", "answer" : "colour"},
    { "question" : "The british spelling of Is it all right if I write you a (check), or would you like cash?.", "answer" : "cheque"},
    { "question" : "The british spelling of The traffic in the (center) of town is terrible this time of day ?.", "answer" : "centre"},
    { "question" : "The british spelling of I haven't met our new (neighbor) yet, Have you?.", "answer" : "neighbour"},
    { "question" : "The british spelling of I missed football (practice) this morning. I wasn't well?.", "answer" : "practice"},
    { "question" : "The british spelling of I hate quiz (programs). Could we change the channel?.", "answer" : "programmes"},
    { "question" : "The british spelling of Come and have a look. I've installed a new (program) in my computer?.", "answer" : "program"},
    { "question" : "The british spelling of Do you think British (humor) is very different from American humor?.", "answer" : "humour"},
    { "question" : "Which preposition does you use after the verb consist?.", "answer" : "of+(something)", "example" : "The exam consist on two parts; a written test and an oral."},
    { "question" : "Which preposition does you use after the verb concentrate?.", "answer" : "on+(doing)(something)", "example" : "It is difficult to concentrate on your work with all this noise", "example2" : "I'd like to concentrate more on improving my writing skills"},
    { "question" : "Which preposition does you use after the verb contribute?.", "answer" : "to+(something)", "example" : "I'd like to thank everyone who contributed to the success of this project"},
    { "question" : "Which preposition does you use after the verb depend?.", "answer" : "on+(someone/something)", "example" : "The size of the grant you get depends on you your income"},
    { "question" : "Which preposition does you use after the verb insist?.", "answer" : "on+(doing)(something)", "example" : "You should always insist on a test drive before buying a car","example2" : "It was joe who insisted on bringing a picnic"},
    { "question" : "Which verb + preposition fit in the sentence : You have to just ignore the crowd and ___ the game?.", "answer" : "concentrate on"},
    { "question" : "Which verb + preposition fit in the sentence : If the goods are faulty you should ___ a refund?.", "answer" : "insist on"},

    { "question" : "Which verb + preposition fit in the sentence : The visitor park ___ maps and guides to local attractions?.", "answer" : "consists on"},
    { "question" : "Which verb + preposition fit in the sentence : The cost of insurance will ___ you age, driving record and type of car?.", "answer" : "depend on"},
    { "question" : "Which verb + preposition fit in the sentence : Scientists believe that carbon dioxide emissions ___ global warming?.", "answer" : "contribute to"},
    { "question" : "Which verb + preposition fit in the sentence : I think that the police should ___ more __ preventing crime?.", "answer" : "concentrate more on"},
    { "question" : "Which verb + preposition fit in the sentence : We all went out to dinner and Ben ___ paying for the whole meal?.", "answer" : "insist on"},
    { "question" : "Which verb + preposition fit in the sentence : The president ___ his advisers to keep him up-to-date with the facts?.", "answer" : "depends on"},

    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to locate?.", "answer" : "to access websites"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to make a copy of files in case of a computer problem?.", "answer" : "to back up files"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to start a computer?.", "answer" : "to boot up"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to mark a webpage for future reference?.", "answer" : "to bookmark a webpage"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to look at websites?.", "answer" : "to browse websites"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)an expert computer user?.", "answer" : "a computer buff"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to suddenly stop working?.", "answer" : "to crash"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to move text or images from one place in a document to another place?.", "answer" : "to cut and paste"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)a computer that isn’t portable and remains in situ on a desk?.", "answer" : "a desktop PC"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary) to edit digital materials like audio or video files?.", "answer" : "digital editing"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to save a copy of a file from the internet to your own device?.", "answer" : "download (podcasts)"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to type the address of a website into the address bar of your browser?.", "answer" : "to enter a web address"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)a technological tool like a mobile phone or camera?.", "answer" : "a gadget"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to start using the Internet?.", "answer" : "to go online"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)powerful computer with top quality components?.", "answer" : "high-spec (laptop)"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)Internet safety?.", "answer" : "Internet security"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)a network of connected computers within an organisation that is not accessible by unauthorised visitors?.", "answer" : "intranet"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to find your way around a website?.", "answer" : "to navigate a website"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)the software that tells the computer how to work?.", "answer" : "operating system"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)send an email with an accompanying file?.", "answer" : "send an attachment"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)media used to interact with other people such as Facebook or Twitter?.", "answer" : "social media"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to look at a series of websites one after the other?.", "answer" : "to surf the web"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)somebody who has an interest in technology?.", "answer" : "a techie"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to obtain a more powerful or feature-rich computer or piece of software?.", "answer" : "to upgrade"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to see and hear people from different locations using the Internet?.", "answer" : "video conferencing"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)a public place where you can access the Internet?.", "answer" : "wireless hotspot"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)a network where users can access the Internet without the use of fixed cables?.", "answer" : "wireless network"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)producing written texts on a computer?.", "answer" : "word processing"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)an event where various athletics sports are held?.", "answer" : "an athletics meeting"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)a running track?.", "answer" : "an athletics track"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)an away game?.", "answer" : "a football match played in the opposing teams stadium"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)a brisk walk?.", "answer" : "a fast walk"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to do judo?.", "answer" : "not go or play"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)a football fan?.", "answer" : "someone who likes football"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)a fitness programme?.", "answer" : "a schedule of activities to keep fit"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)a football match?.", "answer" : "a game of football"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)the surface on which you play football (as opposed to a stadium, which is the building)?.", "answer" : "a football pitch"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)a period in the year when football is played?.", "answer" : "a football season"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to get into shape?.", "answer" : "to become fit"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to go jogging?.", "answer" : "to run around the streets"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)a home game?.", "answer" : "a football match played in the teams own stadium"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to keep fit?.", "answer" : "to stay in good physically condition"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to not be physically fit?.", "answer" : "to be out of condition"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to achieve the best personal result so far in a sport?.", "answer" : "a personal best"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)a sports coach that helps you on a one-to-one basis?.", "answer" : "a personal trainer"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to play tennis/football?.", "answer" : "not do or go"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to run a distance of 42.195 Kilometres?.", "answer" : "to run the marathon"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to run the marathon?.", "answer" : "to run a distance of 42.195 Kilometres"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)a ticket that gives you entry to most of a team’s home games during the sporting year?.", "answer" : "a season ticket"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to achieve the best result in a sport?.", "answer" : "to set a record"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)a public building where people can do various sports?.", "answer" : "a sports centre"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)the equipment and services needed to do a sport?.", "answer" : "sports facilities"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)the surface where you play squash/tennis/badminton sports?.", "answer" : "a squash/tennis/badminton court"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)exercise that needs a lot of physical effort?.", "answer" : "strenuous exercise"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)a strong swimmer:?.", "answer" : "a good swimmer"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to start doing exercise?.", "answer" : "to take up exercise"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)to train with a lot of effort?.", "answer" : "to train hard"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)Walk with confidence(verb)?.", "answer" : "stride"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)Come from sth(phrase adverb)?.", "answer" : "derive from sth"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)beat very easily(verb)?.", "answer" : "Thrash"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)set of regular fixed habits(Noun)?.", "answer" : "rituals"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)the advantage(phrase)?.", "answer" : "the upper hand"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)crazy(adjective)?.", "answer" : "loopy"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)bad magical spell(noun)?.", "answer" : "curses"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)a force that brings bad luck(noun)?.", "answer" : "jink"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary)famous(adjective)(its collocation is for)?.", "answer" : "renowned"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar Verb  +(Gerund or Infinity)) remember something, then do it?.", "answer" : "remember + to do"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar Verb  +(Gerund or Infinity)) do something and remember it later?.", "answer" : "remember + doing"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar Verb  +(Gerund or Infinity)) forget about something, so you don't do it ?.", "answer" : "forget + to do"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar Verb  +(Gerund or Infinity)) do something and (don't) forget it later ?.", "answer" : "forget + doing"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar Verb  +(Gerund or Infinity)) do something and see what happens(like a experiment)?.", "answer" : "try + doing"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar Verb  +(Gerund or Infinity)) make an effort to do something difficult?.", "answer" : "try + to do"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar Verb  +(Gerund or Infinity)) no longer do something?.", "answer" : "stop + doing"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar Verb  +(Gerund or Infinity)) stop something in order to do something else?.", "answer" : "stop + to do"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar Verb  +(Gerund or Infinity)) do something because it's a good a idea?.", "answer" : "like + to do"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar Verb  +(Gerund or Infinity)) enjoy something(like a hobby)?.", "answer" : "like + doing"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) The mind verb is always followed by gerund, infinity or both?.", "answer" : "gerund"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) The consider is always followed by gerund, infinity or both?.", "answer" : "gerund"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) The try is always followed by gerund, infinity or both?.", "answer" : "both"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) The agree is always followed by gerund, infinity or both?.", "answer" : "infinity"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) The hope is always followed by gerund, infinity or both?.", "answer" : "infinity"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) The begin is always followed by gerund, infinity or both?.", "answer" : "both"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) The decide is always followed by gerund, infinity or both?.", "answer" : "infinity"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) The fail is always followed by gerund, infinity or both?.", "answer" : "infinity"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) The need is always followed by gerund, infinity or both?.", "answer" : "infinity"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) The imagine is always followed by gerund, infinity or both?.", "answer" : "gerund"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) The promise is always followed by gerund, infinity or both?.", "answer" : "infinity"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) The stop is always followed by gerund, infinity or both?.", "answer" : "both"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) The want is always followed by gerund, infinity or both?.", "answer" : "infinity"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) The wish is always followed by gerund, infinity or both?.", "answer" : "infinity"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) The remember is always followed by gerund, infinity or both?.", "answer" : "both"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) The forget is always followed by gerund, infinity or both?.", "answer" : "both"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) The involve is always followed by gerund, infinity or both?.", "answer" : "gerund"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) The refuse is always followed by gerund, infinity or both?.", "answer" : "infinity"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) The practice is always followed by gerund, infinity or both?.", "answer" : "gerund"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) The avoid is always followed by gerund, infinity or both?.", "answer" : "infinity"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) I enjoy (to make / making) things with my hands?.", "answer" : "making"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) I love (to visit / visiting) art galleries?.", "answer" : "visiting"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) I dislike (to work / working) alone?.", "answer" : "working"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) I appreciate (to spend / spending) time alone?.", "answer" : "spending"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) Before I use it, I need (to understand / understanding) how something works?.", "answer" : "to understand"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) I like (to learn / learning) the words of songs?.", "answer" : "learning"},
    { "question" : "(Grammar ) I would like (to speak / speaking) several foreign languages?.", "answer" : "to speak", "note":"With would  it have always use infinity "},
    { "question" : "(Pronunciation ) How  iː is usually spelled  ?.", "answer" : "ee and ea"},
    { "question" : "(Pronunciation ) How  i is usually spelled  ?.", "answer" : "i"},

    { "question" : "(Vocabulary adjective)  worried and nervous ?.", "answer" : "anxious", "answer" : "My mother always gets a bit anxious if we don't arrive when we say we will."},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary adjective)  crying or likely to cry ?.", "answer" : "tearful", "answer" : "Katy's always a bit tearful when it's time to go back to school."},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary adjective)  very pleased ?.", "answer" : "delighted", "answer" : "a delighted audience - I was delighted at/by your news."},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary adjective)  feeling worried about something that you are going to do or that is going to happen ?.", "answer" : "apprehensive", "answer" : "I'm very prehensive about tomorrow's meeting."},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary adjective)  very unhappy?.", "answer" : "miserable", "answer" : "miserable weather"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary adjective)  extremely happy and excited, often because something has happened or been achieved?.", "answer" : "elated", "answer" : "The prince was reported to be elated at/by the birth of his daughter."},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary adjective)  extremely pleased?.", "answer" : "thrilled", "answer" : "I was thrilled that so many people turned up to the party."},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary adjective)  happy or satisfied?.", "answer" : "pleased", "answer" : "I'm pleased to hear you're feeling better."},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary adjective)  nervous and worried and unable to relax?.", "answer" : "tense" , "example" : "She was very tense as she waited for the interview."},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary adjective)  sad and likely to cry?.", "answer" : "weepy" , "example" : "I'd just waved Peter off at the airport and was feeling a bit weepy."},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary adjective)  nervous and not relaxed?.", "answer" : "on edge" , "example" : "Is something wrong? You seem a bit on edge this morning."},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary adjective)  extremely pleased and happy?.", "answer" : "overjoyed" , "example" : "Helen was overjoyed to hear that she had got the job."},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary adjective)  almost crying?.", "answer" : "close to tears" , "example" : "I could see that Sam was	close to tears."},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary adjective)   informal for television?.", "answer" : "telly" , "example" : "What's on telly tonight?"},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary adjective)   feeling pleasure and satisfaction because you or people connected with you have done or got something good?.", "answer" : "proud" , "example" : "I'm very proud to have been involved in this project."},
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary collocations)  means it is sudden and unexpected?.", "answer" : "an overnight success" },
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary collocations)  The film 'Star Wars' (was an overnight ___)?.", "answer" : "success" },
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary collocations)  (I have a burning ___ to) travel  to australia'?.", "answer" : "ambition" },
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary collocations)  When pupils tire of studying, a system of rewards can help (increase student ___) ?.", "answer" : "motivation" },
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary collocations)  Sadly, my attempts to learn Japanese (met with complete ___ )?.", "answer" : "failure" },
    { "question" : "(Vocabulary collocations)  The government (faces the formidable ___ of)  reducing unemployment '?.", "answer" : "challenge" },
    { "question" : "(Speaking  expression)  talk about similarities and differences between  two pictures?.", "answer" : "Both picture show..., but this one..., whereas the other one..." },


];